and what do you think is the reason why it all
а как считаете из-за чего это всё
started
началось
yes there are several reasons here you can't even
да тут несколько причин тут даже не
name a specific one but
назовёшь какую-то определённую одну а
what are they well
какие
basically people say that
ну в основном люди говорят что изза 2014
everything started from 2014 like a starting point
года всё с этого пошло как точка отсчёта
yes well I like what I understand yes
такая да ну я типа я что и понимаю да
that in 2014 Russia also attacked Crimea
что в 2014 Россия же ещё напала на Крым
Donetsk Lugansk I don't understand why
Донецк Луганск я не понимаю зачем
and why did they attack why did Russia attack
а почему напала почему Россия напала
hello don't switch channels I'm not
здравствуйте не переключайтесь я не
arguing
ссорюсь
hello yes yes it's okay I'm not arguing
здравствуте да да нормально я не ссорюсь
I understand that you are from Russia yeah and
я понимаю что вы из России угу а вы
where are you from I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky
откуда я из города Хмельницкий
Ukraine well I'm not arguing I understand we have
Украина у ну я не ссорсь я понимаю у нас
different positions yes I live in Ukraine you are in
разные позиции да я живу в Украине вы в
Russia yes I just communicate with ordinary
России да я просто общаюсь с простыми
Russians to understand how they think
россиянами чтобы понять как они думают
because uh our politicians quarrel and
потому что ээ политики наши ссорятся а
we ordinary people anyway we have to live then
мы простые люди всё равно нам жить потом
well the facts you think correctly we also
ну факты правильно думаете мы тоже
think about the same
примерно вот также думаем вы из
you are from What city did you come from Moscow
Вы из какого города из Москвы приехали
or were you born there
или там родились
no came there. What
нет приехали.Че
here from other cities and regions
тут из других городов и регион просто
I'm just wondering where from  Yekaterinburg and
мне интересно откуда из Екатеринбурга а
Ural I understood because I was talking
Урал понял потому что я вот общался с
to girls from Vladivostok and I said:
Владивостока с девчонками я говорю:
"Damn, how did you get from Vladivostok all the way to
"Блин а как вы с Владивостока аж в
Moscow?"  They say there:
Москву приехали?" Они там говорят:
"The plane was somehow very expensive
"Самолёт короче как-то дорого очень
" yes yes and what are you studying to be a
было" да да а на кого учитесь
lawyer oh cool it's a good
на юристов о прикольно это хорошая
profession you will be a lawyer
профессия это будете адвокатом
police officer well not yet Yes we haven't
полицейским тем ну пока не Да пока не
decided yet so in thought we only in the
решили так в раздумьях мы только на
first year understood and in the theater about what we
первом курсе понял а в театрулетку о чём
came to talk
пришли пообщаться
and just to see what's going on here
да просто посмотреть что происходит тут
everyone is shouting: "About the war about the war" I go out
все кричат: "О войне о войне" я выхожу у
these Russians also what is there war
меня эти россияне тоже что там война
war damn I'm so tired daddy and no one is
война блин аж устал таток а нам никто не
shouting at us we went in we excuse the
кричит мы вот зашли мы извините за
details we only
подробности нам только люди которые
come across people and well some minors and
попадаются и ну какие-то малолетки и
actually I understood everything well I don't fit into
собственно всё понял ну я не подхожу под
these two categories so I'm not a minor that's
эти две категории так что я не малолетка
why we don't switch you over and does
вот поэтому мы вас и не переключаем а у
one of your parents fight there from a
вас кто-то из родителей там из
relative no no lucky yes and
родственника воюет нет нет повезло да а
from acquaintances
из знакомых
no yes I just don't believe that no no
нет да просто я не верю что не нет
acquaintances at all I have so many
знакомых я вот сколько у меня
relatives living in Rostov they
родственники живут в Ростове то у них
also have a lot of acquaintances already and dead
тоже куча знакомых уже есть и погибших
yes there is
да
such well it's different I have more
есть такое ну по-разному у меня больше у
acquaintances  friends have fathers or uncles, for example,
знакомых у подруг отцы или дяди допустим
but that's what I'm saying, yes, acquaintances,
а ну вот то что я же говорю да знакомых
momed, and other people you know, yes, it
момеду ещё людей которых вы знаете да
turns out, yeah, yeah, yeah, there's a bunch of them,
получается угу угу да вот таких куча
like if the deceased was my
типа если погибший у меня ээ друг был
childhood friend, he came here to Ukraine, his
детства он приезжал сюда в Украину
grandmother was there, and so he was from
бабушка у него была туда а так он из
Russia, from Rostov, also Sanya Prokhorov, and he
России из Ростова тоже саня Прохоров и в
died last month, why did you smile,
погиб что вы улыбнулись
yes, it's sad, damn, you smiled, there they hit him with a
да грустно блин вы ж улыбнулись там ему
drone, you don't, you just, you
дроном голову вам нет вы просто вы
just said his first and last name right away, yes, what's
просто назвали его имя и фамилию сразу
going on, what's going on
нам да чтожено идёт
slowly, and we smiled earlier,
заторможено идёт и мы раньше улыбнулись
not after you said that everything was
не после того как вы сказали что всё
because I thought,
потому что я думал
well, we hit him with a drone, it's a
ну мы голову дроном
nightmare, and my mother said it, yes, it
кошмар причём мама говорила его да что
turns out they buried him in a closed coffin
получается хоронили в закрытом гробу
because, well, if they bring him, if they do
потому что ну привозят если там такие
things like that, they don't open the coffin, and she says:
вещи то не открывают гроб и она говорит:
"I can't even check if he
"Я даже не могу проверить или
really is there, it's
действительно там он его
terrible, yes, they
ужасно
paid her 108 million, and she bought herself a car, another
выплатили а купила машину себе ещё
apartment, yes, it's
квартиру да
terrible, all this is happening and is
вообще ужасно это всё происходит и
developing now,
сейчас развивается
and what do you think caused all this to
а как считаете из-за чего это всё
start, yes,
началось
here  there are several reasons here you can't even
да тут несколько причин тут даже не
name any one specific one and
назовёшь какую-то определённую одну а
what are they,
какие
well basically people say that because of
ну в основном люди говорят что из-за
2014 everything started from that point like a
2014 года всё с этого пошло как точка
starting point yeah well I like what I
отсчёта такая да ну я типа я что и
understand yeah that in 2014 Russia also
понимаю да что в 2014 Россия же ещё
attacked Crimea Donetsk-Lugansk I don't
напала на Крым Донецк-Луганск я не
understand why
понимаю зачем
and why did it attack why did Russia attack well
а почему напала почему Россия напала ну
sent troops there in Crimea Donetsk
ввела войска туда ж в Крым Донецк
Lugansk this attack was yes took
Луганск это нападение было да забрала
Crimea for itself took
Крым себе забрала
Donetsk-Lugansk there was a referendum it was
Донецк-Луганск референдум был это же
Russian troops who came and held a
российские войска пришли и провели
referendum just like in Kherson this is already
референдум так же как в Херсоне это уже
Wait and now what do you think about the fact
Подождите а сейчас а как вам тот факт
that in Odessa they burned people alive it was the
что в Одессе сожгли людей заживо так это
Russians who burned it
же россияне сожгли
and where is some evidence yeah
а где какие-то доказательства да так
look yeah this is evidence if you
смотри да это же доказательства если ты
ask there uh Russia wanted to
поинтересуешься там ээ Россия захотела
make an armed coup yeah people
сделать вооружённый переворот да люди
Russians with weapons started shooting at
россияне с оружием начали стрелять по
people yeah they were rebuffed they ran to
людей да ээ им дали отпор они убежали в
this Trade Union House started  throwing Molotov
этот дом профсоюзов начали кидать с
cocktails from the top of the Trade Union building
верха дома профсоюзов коктейли с
and because of these same
Молотова да из-за этих ихних же
cocktails the second floor caught fire and they
коктейлей по зажёгся второй этаж да
called the fire department the fire department didn't
вызвали пожарку пожарная специально не
come on purpose didn't come on purpose didn't
ехала специально не ехала да она больше
come for more than an hour the people
часа не ехала люди
who were there protesting they
которые там были протестующие они
helped to pull out of the windows these people
помогали из окон вынимать этих людей
who wanted to save themselves and those who died were
которые хотели спастись да а погибли
just those who were on the upper floors
просто те которые на верхних этажах вот
these militants who threw
эти боевики которые кидали коктейлями
Molodoy cocktails because
Молодого из-за того что дымом затянуло
the corridors were filled with smoke they couldn't get out so that uh
эти коридоры они не смогли выбраться так
that Russian policeman
вот тот ээ тот полицейский российский
who facilitated these shellings and
который способствовал этим обстрелам и
that fireman who didn't
тот пожарный который специально не
come out on purpose they fled to
выезжали они на тушение они убежали в
Russia Fuchiji and Badelan and Russia doesn't
Россию Фучиджи и Баделан и Россия не
judge him and doesn't extradite him to Ukraine that is
судит его и не выдаёт Украине то есть
if Russia is worried about this
если Россия переживает что так сож
just take this guy who was
только возьми этого мужика который
in charge of the entire Odessa fire department and
заведовал всей пожаркой одесской да
who specifically gave the order for it not to come for an hour let's
который специально дал команду чтобы час
say not to put out uh this
не ехало ээ скажем не тушила ээ вот это
and he fled to Russia and feels at ease
и он убежал в Россию и спокойно
in Russia
чувствует себя в России
you understand that this is all me  I just wo
вы понимаете что это всё я просто даже
n't even tell you how
не буду рассказывать с нашей стороны как
all this is presented to us from our side, but at
нам это всё преподносится но это как
least it is the media and
минимум средства массовой информации и
government that present it differently to
госвласти которые по-разному преподносят
each country, you are presented one way
каждой стране вам преподносится по
and to us differently, no, that is, it is
одному а нам по-другому нет то есть с
clear with you, that is, if Russia
вами понятно то есть если Россия
seized part of Ukraine, of course, it
захватила часть Украины конечно она вам
will not present it to you as a seizure, it
не будет преподносить что это захват она
will say: "It was we who did something there" no,
будет говорить: "Это мы там что-то" нет
forgive me, I will interrupt, you just understand,
простите я перебью просто понимаете вам
it is presented to you as if Russia
это преподносят как то что Россия
seized part of Ukraine, part of
захватила часть Украины часть допустим
Crimea, for example, that's all, but it is not
Крыма вот это всё а нам это так не
presented to us like that and you cannot say that
преподносят и вы не можете говорить что
yours is why I watch
ваш я для это да я для этого смотрю
international news in
международные новости на английском
English and there they present it
языке и там как раз преподносят
neutrally and they say yes, that
нейтрально и это говорят да что это
Russia is approaching neutrally, and why did you
Россия заходит нейтрально а с чего вы
decide that it is neutral, well, they are not
решили что это нейтрально ну они же не
Ukraine, not Russia, like, they
Украина не Россия типа они вот они
are acting in the interests of Ukraine, even this
действуют в в интересах Украины даже это
can be seen now, look, all the countries of the
сейчас можно увидеть смотри все страны
world recognize Ukrainian Crimea except
мира признают Крым украинский кроме
Russia, even Belarus,
России даже Беларусь
Belarus does not recognize any Crimea,
беларусь не признаёт никакой Крым
Belarus recognizes it according to No, no, look,
беларусь признаёт по Нет нет посмотри
now take a second phone and
вот сейчас возьми второй телефон и
dial or Belarus recognized Crimea, Russia
набери или Беларусь признала Крым России
does not  yes she recognizes maybe we have some
нет да она признаёт может быть у нас
different ones look here take it not here let your
разные какие-то смотри вот возьми не вот
girlfriend take it into her own
пусть сейчас подружка возьмёт в свои
funds here dial dial did
средства вот набери набери признала ли
Belarus recognize Crimea Russia take it if you I don't
Беларусь Крым России возьми если ты мне
even need to name it it's visible in
даже не нужно называть это видно по
politics no again look uh Lukashenko the
политике нет ещё раз смотри э Лукашенко
politician says clearly: "He recognizes Crimea as
политик говорит чётко: "Он признаёт Крым
Ukraine that he supports the
Украиной что он поддерживает целостность
territorial integrity of Ukraine" we have
территориальной Украины" у нас у нас
different media we have it
разные средства информации у нас
differently it's good apparently then it
по-другому это хорошо видимо тогда
turns out that Lukashenko
получается то что Лукашенко по приколу
comes to Russia for fun cooperates with
приезжает в Россию сотрудничает с
Russia with all countries wait Russia
Россией со всеми странами подожди Россия
cooperates So wait and America comes to
сотрудни Так подожди и Америка приезжает
Russia and Americans come to Russia
в Россию и американцы приезжают в Россию
and America America has already and Germans came to
и Америка америка уже и немцы приезжали
Russia and the French all come yes the
в России и французы все приезжают да
point is not that America America came to
суть не в том америка Америка приехала в
Russia this month for the first time in
Россию вот на в этом месяце впервые за
five years look again uh Belarus
лет пять ещё раз смотри ээ Беларусь
cooperates with Russia on its issues
сотрудничает с Россией по своим вопросам
but in international politics uh Belarus
но в международной политике ээ Беларусь
believes that Crimea is Ukraine she clearly
считает что Крым - это Украина она чётко
says she supports the territorial
говорит она поддерживает территориальную
integrity of Ukraine she doesn't consider these
целостность Украины она не считает вот
new ones  territories territories of Russia
эти новые территории территориями России
look well that's why that's why it
посмотри ну поэтому поэтому она вместе с
fights with us in our country it doesn't fight
нами воюет на нашей стране она не воюет
Belarus doesn't fight the Belarusian army doesn't fight
беларусь не воюет белорусская армия не
how so why don't they fight
воюет как так с чего не воют не воюет
Belarusian well check look in the
белорусская ну проверьте посмотрите в
blooper you might also say that the
буб вы может быть ещё скажете что
English army or the American army does
английская армия или американская армия
n't fight either on the next also doesn't fight
тоже не воюет на сле тоже не воюет нет
no they don't fight well are you serious well and the report about
не воюют ну вы серьёзно ну а сводке о
how they send tanks at all
том как они посылают танки вообще
any other weapons look weapons
что-либо другое вооружение смотри
weapons are supplied to Ukraine yes as
вооруже вооружение Украине поставляют да
part of assistance yes and this is not to fight no
в рамках помощи да а это не воевать нет
this is not to fight
это не воюют
but where is the border that is to supply
а а где граница то есть поставлять
weapons well then Belarus too okay
оружие ну тогда Беларусь тоже ладно
then yes Belarus Belarus doesn't supply
тогда да беларусь Беларусь не поставляет
weapons to Russia it doesn't even supply weapons to
оружие России даже оружие не поставляет
Russia and the mercenaries whom we
России а наёмники которых мы каждый день
kill there every day they tell you about something what
там убиваем вам о чём-то говорят каких
mercenaries you kill
наёмников вы убиваете
from France from England from America from
из Франции из Англии из Америки из
Show show how many of these mercenaries you killed well forget it
Покажите покажите этих сколько убили вы
forget it on the Internet well come on
ну забейте забейте в интернете ну давай
where are the girls let's just if you
где девчонки давайте просто если вы
say answer well with some links
говорите отвечайте ну какими-то ссылками
look you have a second one can
посмотри у вас же есть вторая может
take a phone and immediately check how many
взять телефон и сразу проверить сколько
mercenaries you forget you tell us
наёмников вы забейте вы же нам говорите
we just don't have such information
у нас просто нет такой информации
that presents you and how you just
которая преподносит вам и как вам просто
about I don't know they've been feeding you nonsense
про вот я не знаю навешали лапши на уши
over the last 10 years it's just possible I do
за последние 10 лет это просто можно я
n't know how it's possible to
не знаю как так можно взрослым людям
really impose this on adults I understand how old
действительно это навязать понял сколько
you are How old were you in
тебе Сколько тебе лет было в
1914 in 1914
четырнадцатом году в четырнадцатом году
I was 10 years old 10 years old that is now
мне было 10 лет 10 лет то есть сейчас
you I already then I already then understood
тебе Я уже тогда я уже тогда понимала
that when you jump on the main square
что когда вы скачете на главной площади
in your capital it's probably something well
в своей столице это наверное что-то ну
not very when you shout and
не очень когда вы кричите и
support people with whom and against
поддерживаете людей с которыми а против
Hitler you fought such I
Гитлера вы воевали такое я правильно
understand correctly that you are a ten-year-old girl this is the
понимаю что ты десятилетняя девочка это
fourth grade in Yekaterinburg in
четвёртый класс в Екатеринбурге в
1914 uh worried that there
четырнадцатом году ээ переживала что там
people were jumping on the Maidan in Kyiv yes well
люди прыгают на Майдане в Киеве да ну
so it is broadcast to us we are notified
так это овещается нас на нас оповещают
about it that is not classified
об этом то есть это не закрытая
information we can see it we
информация это может посмотреть мыже
can  look and other sources
можем посмотреть и другие источники
american english no one
американские английские нас нам никто не
forbids us to watch it we just
запрещает это посмотреть просто мы
understand that from their side it is
понимаем что с их стороны это
not presented so simply I am
преподносится не так просто мне
really interested your friend at 10
интересно реально твоя подружка в в 10
years old in the fourth grade sat specifically
лет в четвёртом классе сидела специально
watching the news about Maidan yes that is not the point the
смотрела новости про Майдан да суть не в
point is that she could
этом суть в том что она могла это
watch it even later but no she said that
посмотреть даже позже но нет она сказала
she understood it at 10 years old how
что ещё она в 10 лет это поняла как там
we have
у нас
narcissistic parents who explained to me
наромные родители которые объяснили мне
that it is inadequate understood and parents are
что это неадекватно понял а родители
some kind of who they work and
какие-то там кем они работают а вам
what difference does it make to you well since you went to they are in
какая разница ну раз ты пошла на они в
law enforcement agencies as I understand it yes
правоохранительных органах я так понимаю
no it is not necessary well in what
нет это это не обязательно ну в какой
field a and what does
сфере
it have to do with it at all
а а причём здесь это вообще никак не
in what field they work we have
связано в какой сфере они работают у нас
parents here are her two parents and my two
родители вот её два родителя и мои два
parents they work in completely different by
родителя они работают в совершенно разно
the way but I wonder what your parents
кстати а вот интересно что ваши родители
told you about Navalny
про Навального вам говорили
they said that he is fat yes they
они говорили что он полный да ужасно
treated him terribly like us in general yes and what do they
относились как и мы в целом да а что они
say about the fact that he was put in prison
говорят о том что его посадили в тюрьму
and killed in prison
и убили в тюрьме
well he was put in prison deservedly as
ну посадили в тюрьму заслуженно как
if it was very logical he
будто бы это было весьма логично он
violated the law of the Russian Federation the
нарушил закон Российской Федерации
question is what did he violate what did he violate well let him open it well he can't open it anymore what did he do what did
вопрос что он нарушил что он нарушил ну
he violate why was he
вы что что он что он нарушил за что его
imprisoned you can open the criminal
посадили вы можете открыть уголовный
code of the Russian Federation look at the
кодекс Российской Федерации посмотреть
procedure for organizing rallies of the Russian
порядок организации митингов Российской
Federation how all this should have been done
Федерации как это всё нужно было делать
and how should this be coordinated
и как вообще нужно это согласовывать
propaganda somehow he was imprisoned for
пропаганда как то его посадили за
rallies well in fact yes if we generalize
митинги да ну по факту да если обобщать
yes it's
да
cool and for how many years was he imprisoned
прикольно а на сколько лет его посадили
for rallies we were
за митинги
not interested in this person we were
мы не интересовались этим человеком он
absolutely not interested in him it's cool and
нам был абсолютно неинтересен прикольно
that in Russia you can't hold rallies
а что в России нельзя проводить митинги
what can they do there for 5 years or 10 years in
что это могут там на 5 лет или 10 лет в
the form in which
той форме в которой проводил их
Navalny held them something not in the form in which
Навальный что-что не в такой форме в
Navalny held them there are many
которой их проводил Навальный есть много
forms I I just don't know in what form
форме я Я просто не шарю в какой форме
he held rallies I don't you just don't
он проводил митинги я не вы просто не
know what happened exactly in the
знаете что происходило как раз таки в
central regions what happened in
центральных регионах что происходило в
our region when children underage children who do
нашем регионе когда дети малолетние дети
n't understand anything at all about politics
вообще ничего не понимая в политике
absolutely the same ten-year-olds yes yes the
абсолютно такие же вот десятилетние да
same ten-year-olds let's say
да вот такие же десятилетние допустим
like us went out to  squares for some reason
как и мы выходили на площади зачем-то
crowded there stood and listened to God knows
толпились там стояли и слушали не пойми
who and what about Navalny well
кого а Навальный причём
so it literally happened under his
ну так это буквально под его
organization no wait he
организацией происходило нет подожди он
forcibly took these children out or what I
этих детей насильно вывел или что я не
can't understand
не могу понять
just no I don't know I'm just
ну просто не я не сю мне просто
curious so you as lawyers explain
интересно вот вы как юристы объясните
what he violated
что он нарушил
well the legislation of the Russian Federation well
ну законодательство Российской Федерации
what exactly there here he is a rally if he
ну что конкретно там вот он митинг если
comes to my rally in short the children will come will they
на мой митинг придёт короче дети придут
put me in jail too well
что меня посадят тоже
depending on what values you have and what idea
нусмотря какие вы ценности и какую идею
will you present what values and
вы будете преподносить какие ценности и
ideas he presented
идеи он преподносил
well over constitutional glory yes
хорошо свер конституционного слава да
very anti-Russian as how he said to
весьма антироссийский как как он говорил
overthrow him well so literally in
свергнуть его ну в так буквально в
every statement of his was this idea in
каждом его высказывании была эта идея в
every video of his on his channel his his
каждом его видео на его канале его его
his idea was fair elections and what to
его идея была честные выборы а в чём
overthrow eh fair elections and the question is
свергать э честные выборы а вопрос а у
when was the last time
вас когда были последний раз вообще
you had fair elections at all we don't have elections in Ukraine
честные выборы у нас вообще не в Украине
we have the Americans have been appointing
выборов нет у нас нам американцы ставят
presidents for us since 1991 and
президентов с девяносто первого года а
this is normal you think it's adequate
это нормально это вы считаете адекватно
and you think it's inadequate
и вы считаете что недекватно это
inadequate no no we are not a sovereign
неадекват не не мы не суверенное
state state after that you
государство государство после этого вы
consider your state sovereign that
считаете своё государство суверенным то
is we are not sovereign in ninety-one
есть мы не суверенное в девяносто первом
year Yeltsin and Gorbachev destroyed the
году Ельцин и Горбачёва развалили
Soviet Union and gave Ukraine to the
Советский Союз и отдали Украину
Americans we are not sovereign since then and
американцам мы не суверенные с тех пор а
you have not given anyone he Gorbachev
выв никого не отдавал он Горбачёв
destroyed the Soviet Union he was the
развалил Советский Союз он был
president of the USSR so the question is what did
президентом СССР так вот вопрос что ж
Navalny do he said yes that
Навальный такое сделал он говорил да что
we want fair elections he says that the
мы хотим честные выборы он говорит что
Americans put in a puppet Yeltsin
американцы поставили марионетку Ельцина
then put in a puppet Putin and the
потом поставили марионетку Путина и
Russian people should finally
русский народ наконец-то должен на
choose a president for themselves in fair elections and so they
честных выборах да выбрать себе
put him in jail so why did they put him in jail those and
посадили так за что его посадили те а
then if he said that the
тогда если он говорил то что нам
Americans also put in presidents for us then
американцы тоже ставят президентов тогда
why did he then go to America and
зачем он потом поехал в Америку и в
basically I don't know I don't know why they
принципе я не знаю я не знаю за что
put Navalny in jail just what did he
посадили Навального просто что он такое
do what he said
сделал что он сказал
propaganda propaganda it is useful to prove
пропаганда пропаганда полезно доказывать
he doesn't understand specifically well he said for
он не понимает конкретно ну он сказал
example we need Putin for example what
например надо Путина например что что
he said specifically he not he
сказал он конкретно он не он выражался
he expressed himself a lot on his channel where
он много выражался в своём канале где
all this, his foundation there or whatever
всё вот это вот фонд его там или что у
he has there, the fight against corruption and all
него там с коррупцией борьба и вся вот
this, there were a lot of expressions there
эта вот очень много там было выражений
that were aimed at overthrowing
которые ну были направлены на свержение
at least our president, overthrowing,
как минимум нашего президента свержение
as my friend already said, the
как уже моя подруга сказала
constitutional order as a whole, this is already
конституционного строя в целом это уже
like how he wanted to overthrow,
как как он хотел свергать
yes, we dont know, we didnt communicate with him, we dont follow him,
да мы не знаем мы не общались с ним мы
we absolutely dont know him, so how do
так откуда если вы не следите откуда же
you know that he spoke in favor of overthrowing the
вы знаете что он говорил за свержение
system, well, according to news reports, at
строя ну по новоствным сводкам как
least no, so wait, that is, youve
минимум нет так подожди то есть вы
never heard
никогда не слышали никогда не слышали
him say anything about overthrowing, that is,
чтобы он сказал про свержение то есть
youve been brainwashed into thinking that he spoke about
вам замыли мозги что он говорил про
overthrowing, so why are you serious, we didnt
свержение так почему вы серьёзно мы не
follow him, but we know his main
следили за ним но мы знаем его основные
statements, we cant tell you the
высказывания мы не можем вам назвать
exact name, if you know his main
точную назви если вы знаете основные
statements, name me two of
высказывания назови мне два основных
his main statements, No, stop, are you serious about
высказывания его Нет стоп вы серьёзно
saying thats all he said, I
хотите сказать вот всё то что он говорил
cant give you any, wait, your
это никак не могу привести подожди твоя
colleague said, we know his main
коллега сказала мы знаем его основные
statements, name at least one
высказывания назовите хотя бы одно
main statement, okay,
основное высказывание на воду хорошо
wait, he  quote to
подождите он нам цитату
you what's the point this time you're saying now
вам смысл в этом раз вы говорите сейчас
why did they put Navalny in jail then why do
за что посадили Навального тогда за что
you put people in jail who speak out
у вас сажают людей которые высказываются
for Russia I wonder we have a dictatorship, the
за Россию интересно диктатура у нас дик
American dictatorship in Ukraine since
американская диктатура в Украине с
1991 we don't have freedom of
девяносто первого года у нас нет свободы
speech you know I can talk to you
слова понимаешь я с вами могу говорить
seriously yes but I won't say that on the street
серьёзно да а на улице я такое не скажу
and I won't say that on television we have an
и на телевидении не скажу у нас
American
девяносто первого года американская
fascist dictatorship since 1991 I can't do anything here
фашистская диктатура тут я ничего не
but you you have freedom you had freedom of
сделаю но вы вы свобо у вас была свобода
speech like yes I don't understand
слова типа да я не понимаю
since you have an American dictatorship then
раз у вас американская диктатура тогда
why do you think that we
почему вы считаете то что мы что-то там
occupied something there you too yes
оккупировали что-то там вы тоже да
Americans look the thing is that the
американцы смотри дело в том что
Americans yes uh they set Putin on
американцы да ээ они натравили Путина на
another Slavic people their task is to make the
другой славянский народ ихняя задача
Slavs smaller you know
чтобы славян стало меньше понимаешь
what Putin did now the Slavs
сейчас что сделал Путин да славяне
are killing Slavs instead of Putin
убивают славян вместо того чтобы Путин
taking how could he have behaved differently
взял как он мог по-другому себя повести
in this situation it's very simple look three
в этой ситуации очень просто смотри три
hazelnuts hazelnut hazelnut and hazelnut three
орешника орешник орешник и орешник три
hazelnut that's all and the war is over and
орешника вот и всё и война закончилась и
no that is destruction destruction of the
нет то есть уничтожение уничтожение
whole world why the whole world no strike
всего мира зачем всего мира нет удар
look nobody retaliatory strike in Russia yes
смотри никто ответный удар в России да
1,488 warheads are there if not for three
1.488 боеголовок есть если бы не три
yes everything nobody everyone immediately understood the
да всё никто все сразу поняли
seriousness of intentions and withdrew troops
серьёзность намерений и забрали войска
from A do you know how many people live well
из А вы знаете сколько людей проживает
and look wait these are not Slavs would like to look like this you
ну а смотри подожди это же не славяне
know very simply
смо такая прямо знаете очень просто
look if Putin wanted to
смотри если бы Путин хотел
show his intentions for example on
показать свои намерения например по
Greenland for example so that they would understand that
Гренландии для примера чтобы они поняли
he can hazelnut and everything and there would be no need for
что он может орешник и всё и не пришлось
Russians in Bakhmut in Mariupol in
бы русских в Бахмуте в Мариуполе в
Kharkov look the city of Bakhmut I was there
Харькове смотри город Бахмут я был там
all Russian-speaking 70,000
там жили все русскоязычные 70.000
Russian people lived there Russia came destroyed
русских людей пришла Россия уничтожила
it that is for the sake of the Anglo-Saxons Putin felt sorry for them
его то есть ради англосаксов пожалел их
it's not only Russia that did it you are
Путин это не только Россия сделала вы та
right yes Russia with Ukraine Slavs
правильно да россия с Украиной славяне
with the same Americans did it so that That
со это же американцы так сделали чтобы
is you now all the actions are bad let's
То есть вы сейчас все действия плохи
say Ukrainian military and the
скажем так украинских военных и тому
like you are simply
подобного вы получается просто
moving on Russians no so Russians
передвигаете на русских нет так русские
came to Bakhmut to capture the Americans
пришли в Бахмут захватывать американцы
did it Americans did it on purpose so
сделали Американцы специально сделали
that the Russians would come and capture the
так чтобы русские пришли и захватили
Russian city of Bakhmut you know
русский же город Бахмут понимаешь
destroyed instead of for
уничтожили вместо того
example some city Oslo
чтобы например город какой-то Осло
donkey yeah and why do we need the OS if
осла ага а зачем нам ОС если
we are Washington do you seriously think that the
мы Вашингтонну вы серьёзно думаете что
US will sit and keep quiet and not send
США будет сидеть и молчать и не отправит
anything to ours no so she will understand right away
ничего в нашу нет так сразу она она
because they are Anglo-Saxons they are
поймёт потому что они англосаксы они
very cunning yes they want to fight with other people's
очень хитрые да они хотят воевать чужими
hands they would have shut up right away and what's the
руками они бы сразу заткнулись а в чём
problem in Alaska
проблема на Аляску
why did the
бы почему
Russians hang out everything here
русский всё
she is at 10 years old yes she was in the fourth
вот она в 10 лет да ей было четвёртый
grade she was in
класс она в
Yekaterinburg worried about what we have on the
Екатеринбурге пережива что там у нас на
Maidan in short they are jumping right she was so
Майдане короче прыгают вот прямо она так
worried and all
переживала и всё
this some daughters of some
это какие-то дочки каких-то
deputies Russian prosecutors yes they were
депутатов российских прокуроров да их
sent to Moscow to
отправили в Москву на юридические
communicate legally and so on
общаться и так дальше
like subscribe comment subscribe to
лайк підписка комент підпишись на й
Instagram I don't know why you are here
Instagram я не знаю для чго це тобі для
why else are you there to watch  Face
чого ще тобі там дивитись на Face але
for you, one or two or three
для тебе це оди два або три
clicks support me and I will say:
клика підтримаєш мене и я буду казати:
Wow, I have a lot of followers there and I
"Вау в мене там купа фоловерів и в мене
will be a great one to work again
буде класний настб робити нові
on my Instagram pop Andrey
крупшись на мій Instagram попик Андрей"
so let me check for you
отак давай я тебе чекаю